不  他的记忆不是被搅乱
No, his memories weren't jumbled.
而是被...置换了
They were...replaced.
有一部分被置换了
Just some of them.
该你了
You're up.
-不用了  -来吧
- No, I'm okay. - Nah, come on.
这对你有帮助
It's good for you.
能训练你大脑和手的协调性
Helps your brain and hands learn to get their act together.
被置换的记忆  被搅乱的记忆
Replaced memories, jumbled memories...
他怎么还能保持清醒
How the hell is he supposed to keep everything together?
要是他忘了他是哪边的人了呢
What if he forgets what team he's on?
我希望我的老大不要乱糟糟的
You know, I like my bosses un-jumbled at all times.
他没有乱糟糟的  会好的
Yeah, he is, or he will be.
他会恢复的  他以前就恢复过
He'll recover. He did before.
而且大脑永远不会删除文件
Besides, brains never delete files.
它们只是失去了联系
They just lose connections.